威尔 · 森特斯: 这条蓝线下面是
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Below
this blue line here is
就是那些不存在的东西
gonna be the things that are not
在 JavaScript 中发生的事情。
happening in JavaScript at all.
它们将成为我们网页浏览器的特性。
They're gonna be our web browser features.
它们是在 JavaScript 中吗？
Are they in JavaScript?
不不不绝对不行。
No, no, no, no, absolutely not.
跟平常一样。
Up here same as normal.
这是 JavaScript 中的全局内存。
Here's our global memory in JavaScript.
就是这个。
There it is.
这是我们的调用堆栈。
Here's our call stack over here.
就是这个。
There it is.
好了，一号线，一号线,
And here we go, line one, line one,
马克，一号线，我们该怎么办，朋友？
Mark, line one, what do we do my friend?
马克: 我们正在定义一个函数 printHello。
&gt;&gt; Mark: We're defining
a function printHello.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 马克说得很好，他只是回来了，然后直奔主题,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Very nice from Mark, he
just came back in and straight on point,
马克说得太好了。
excellent from Mark.
我们正在定义一个函数 printHello，就是这个。
We're defining a function printHello,
there it is.
被拯救，美丽。
Saved, beautiful.
好吧，现在事情变得有趣了。
Okay, now things get interesting.
现在我们进入下一行。
Now we head to the next line.
这条线在干什么？
What is this line doing?
我们要，我删除了大部分，所以我要把它放回去。
We are going to, I erased much of it so
I'm gonna put it back on.
但是我们的 web 浏览器是 JavaScript 和 JavaScript 的结合
But we had our web Browser being
a combination of JavaScript and
我们从 JavaScript 中获取标签的浏览器特性。
browser features that we get labels for
from within JavaScript.
看看这个，setTimeout 是 web 浏览器中计时器的标签。
And look at this one here, setTimeout is
a label for a timer in the web browser.
那么让我们开始 JavaScript 的第一行
So let's do our first line of JavaScript
这只是一个命令,
that's really just gonna be a command,
网页浏览器功能的信息。
a message down to the web
browser features.
在 JavaScript 中它甚至什么都做不了。
It's not even gonna do
anything in JavaScript.
在这里，setTimeout。
Here it is, setTimeout.
好了我们开始吧。
All right, here we go.
我可以请人到白板上来吗，马克？
Am I allowed to have someone
come to the whiteboard, Mark?
不，好吧，伊森，这是你的荣幸，朋友。
No, all right, Ethan,
it is your honored moment my friend.
过来。
Come up here.
伊森: (笑)威尔 · 森坦斯: 拿着那支蓝色的钢笔。
&gt;&gt; Ethan: [LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Take the blue pen.
伊森: 我的天啊。
&gt;&gt; Ethan: My goodness.
Will Sentance: 然后在 setTimeout 在 JavaScript 中的位置给我画一条线
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: And draw a line for
me from where setTimeout is in JavaScript
它的后果将会在网页浏览器中显现。
to where its consequence
will be in the web browser.
给我画一条线，从它在 JavaScript 中的位置到它的结果可能出现的位置
Draw me a line from where it is in
JavaScript to where its consequence might
在这块黑板上。
be on this blackboard here.
伊森: 好吧 威尔 · 森塔斯: 这是一个很长的
&gt;&gt; Ethan: All right.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: It's a long
直线。
straight line.
议长4: (笑)威尔 · 森坦斯: 他说得对吗？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: [LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Is he right?
让我们为他鼓掌。
Let's give him a huge hand.
观众: (掌声)威尔 · 森坦斯: 谢谢你，伊森。
&gt;&gt; Audience: [APPLAUSE]
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Thank you, Ethan.
伊森给你一个好的。
One up from Ethan, all right.
不，好吧，很好。
No, okay, good.
不，那很好，很好。
No, that's perfect, perfect.
我们在网页浏览器中设置了一个计时器。
We have set up a timer in the web browser.
这就是了，与 JavaScript 无关。
There it is,
nothing to do with JavaScript.
在浏览器中有我们的计时器。
In the web browser there's our timer.
布雷登有什么消息,
Now, what information Brayden,
我们需要一个成功的计时器吗？
do we need for
this to be a successful timer?
布雷登: printHello。
&gt;&gt; Brayden: printHello.
威尔 · 森特斯: 是的，是的，当然。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, yeah, sure.
但还有更重要的事吗，杰夫？
But something even more important, Jeff?
杰夫: 持续时间。
&gt;&gt; Jeff: Duration.
威尔 · 森特斯: 计时器的持续时间，完全正确。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Duration of the timer,
exactly.
也就是1000毫秒。
Which is 1,000 milliseconds.
就是这样，1000毫秒。
So there we go, 1,000 milliseconds.
也就是说，暂停，结果,
That is to say, timeouts, consequences,
所有的结果都在浏览器里，什么功能？
consequences all in the web browser,
what feature?
这是计时器，需要1000毫秒。
It's the timer and
it's gonna take 1,000 milliseconds.
就是这个。
There it is.
现在，我们不是无缘无故地设置一个计时器，我们是这样设置的
Now, we're not setting up a timer for
no reason, we're setting it up so
我们可以在它完成后运行这个函数。
we can run the function on its completion.
所以让我们来看看完成时和完成时,
So let's have over here On Completion and
On Completion,
马特，我们希望发生什么？
Matt, what are we gonna
want to have happen?
我们想运行 printHello。
We want to run printHello.
我们想打电话，我们想用 JavaScript 运行 printHello。
&gt;&gt; Matt: We want to call, we want to
run printHello back in JavaScript.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 所以你要抓住 printHello 函数，和
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: So you're gonna grab
the printHello function as well, and
就是这儿，我们的公主。
there it is, our printHello.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 完成之后，美丽。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: On completion,
beautiful.
现在，它完成了吗？
Now, is it complete?
这就是为什么我们必须在我们的谜题中加入一个新的部分。
And this is wherefore we're gonna
have to add a new part to our puzzle.
那是我的绿色笔，代表时间的流逝。
And that's my green pen that
represents time passing.
所以我们要引爆它
So we're setting this off
大概是0，很漂亮,
at roughly 0, beautiful,
大概0毫秒。
roughly 0 milliseconds.
这时，这一行触发了后台的工作。
That's when this line triggers
the work in the background.
这个计时器，这个1000毫秒的计时器 Dan,
At 0 millisecond folk, is this timer,
this 1,000 milliseconds timer Dan,
完成了吗？
is it complete?
阿丹: 不是的 威尔 · 森塔斯: 不是，不是。
&gt;&gt; Dan: It is not.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: It is not, it is not.
但是 JavaScript facade 函数完成了它的工作了吗？
But has the JavaScript facade
function done its work?
的确如此。
It has.
它唯一的工作是做什么？
Its only job was to do what?
它唯一的任务是做什么，布雷登？
Its only job was to do what, Brayden?
布雷登: 设定时间。
&gt;&gt; Brayden: Set the timer.
威尔 · 森特斯: 把计时器设置在？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Set the timer up in the?
浏览器 在网页浏览器中。
&gt;&gt; Brayden: Browser.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: In the web browser.
这是它唯一的工作。
That's its only job.
那么在那个时候我们能做些什么呢,
So what can we do at that moment
after setting up that work,
一毫秒之内我们可以移动到哪条线上 Todd？
well, at one millisecond,
we can move onto what line, Todd?
我们可以直接走哪条线？
What line can we move straight onto?
托德: 控制台记录我第一。
&gt;&gt; Todd: Console log me first.
我们可以直接移动到控制台日志我第一！
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: We can move
straight onto console log Me first!
大家看看这个。
Look at this, people.
直接到控制台登录我第一。
Straight onto console log me first.
在那里，我会把我们的控制台放在这里。
There it is, and
I will put our console over here.
如果有人告诉我应该是蓝色的，因为我哥哥
And if anybody tells me it should
be in blue, because my brother
是的，我知道，但我们要把它放在这里，我先。
feature yes, I know but
we'll put it over here, me first.
看看这个，是不是很漂亮，伙计们？
And look at that,
isn't that beautiful, people?
在一毫秒的时间里，顺便说一句,
At one millisecond, and
to be clear by the way,
这些时间就是我所说的序数。
these timings here
are what I call ordinal.
这意味着他们在向我们展示事情发生的顺序
That means that like they're showing
us the order of things happening
实际上下一句话需要十亿分之一秒的时间
actually would take like nanoseconds
to do that next line, but
还有一段时间比较容易，那就是我。
there's a sort of a milliseconds
to be easier and there is me.
我第一个在一毫秒和民间,
Me first at one millisecond and folk,
我们所有的常规 JavaScript 代码都完成了。
all of our regular
JavaScript code is done.
但是在浏览器的后台，时间在流逝，滴答。
But in the background in the web browser,
time is passing, tick tock.
滴答滴答就在那儿。
Tick, tock, there it is.
托德: 是的。
&gt;&gt; Todd: Yeah.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 向我们最喜欢的大型箱式零售商大声疾呼吧，就是它了。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Shout out to our
favorite big box retailer, there it is.
观众: (笑)威尔 · 森坦斯: 在网页浏览器中,
&gt;&gt; Audience: [LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: In the web browser,
时间在流逝。
time is passing.
在1000毫秒时，凯拉，我们认为会发生什么？
And at 1,000 milliseconds, Kayla,
what do we think is gonna have happened?
我们的计时器完成了吗？
Is our timer complete?
是的。
&gt;&gt; Kayla: Yeah.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 是的 它会调用函数。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: It is.
&gt;&gt; Kayla: It's gonna call the function.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 她说得很对。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: She is spot on.
计时器已经完成
The timer is complete and
这个函数会回到 JavaScript。
that function there is gonna
head right back into JavaScript.
我们要把它放在调用堆栈上，因为这是我们在调用上运行函数的方式
We're gonna put it on the call stack, cuz
that's how we run a function on the calls
随着时间的推移，时间过去了，时间过去了。
as it goes, and look, tons of time
has passed, tons of time has passed.
1,000 milliseconds，JavaScript with the help of the web
At 1,000 milliseconds,
JavaScript with the help of the web
浏览器将以某种方式自动开始执行 printHello。
browser is going to somehow automatically
start executing, printHello.
这对民众有什么影响呢？
And what's that going to do folk?
它将在控制台和控制台中显示。
That's going to put on the console and
display in the console.
你好在1000毫秒的时候,
Hello, at 1,000 milliseconds,
我们得到了你好，人们，就是这样。
we get Hello, and people, that's it.
设定暂停，我们需要知道的就是设定暂停并不是真的一无所有
Set timeout, all we need to know really is
that set timeout ain't really has nothing
做一个 JavaScript 代码。
to do a JavaScript at all.
现在，从技术上来说，它在 JavaScript 中确实有一个返回值，不仅仅是这样
Now, technically it does have a return
value in JavaScript is not just not that
有趣就像定时器的 ID。
interesting is like an ID for the timer.
这就是真正的 Java 设置超时时间。
That's real Java set timeout is all
the way down here in the web browser.
这才是真正的目的。
That's it's real purpose.
一旦我们意识到这点我想是的,
Once we realized that, I guess yeah,
设置一个 web 浏览器功能需要花费大量的时间，而且是零毫秒,
that bit setting up a web browser feature
takes like that time, is zero millisecond,
一毫秒意味着我们可以继续前进。
one millisecond meaning
we can plow straight on.
看看这个，我们要直接犁地
Look at this, we're going to
plow straight on to running at
先在我身上安慰一下，然后一分钟一秒。
one minute second straight
after a console on me first.
然后在后台，我们的时间都是在网页浏览器中完成的,
And then in the background, our time is
doing all this stuff in the web browser,
与 JavaScript 无关。
nothing to do with JavaScript.
只是 web 浏览器众多特性中的一个,
JavaScript is just one of the many
features of the web browser,
网页浏览器是一个不可思议的应用程序，坐在那里，就这样。
the web browser is an incredible
application sitting down there, that's it.